dtcc.edu 2017-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Delaware Technical Community College

Thank you for visiting the Delaware Technical Community College Website. Delaware Tech respects the privacy of all website visitors and is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all individuals who access the College website. This privacy policy statement describes what information we collect and how that information is protected and used.

We do not collect personal information from you when you visit the website unless you voluntarily choose to provide such information to the College. Our web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website. Recognition of this information does not result in the identification of your email address or other personal information as that information is not recognized by our server.

In order to improve the content of our website, we utilize Google Analytics to collect information which specifically includes the volume of visits to the website, the dates, times and web pages accessed. Personal information shall not be identified and this data will not be shared with third party organizations.

Any information you voluntarily provide through email or through our electronic forms will only be used for the purpose for which it is intended. We encrypt all transactions on our website through secured socket layers (SSL) which can be verified by the lock icon and “https” displayed on the browser address bar. Personal information will not be shared with other organizations, unless required by state or federal law.

To deliver dynamic services and enhanced functionality to site visitors, Delaware Technical Community College web pages may provide links to external web sites and third party sites outside of the Delaware Tech domain. Websites and other third party sites not owned, controlled or managed by Delaware Tech are not bound by the College’s Privacy Policy and, as such, Delaware Tech is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. The destination links on Delaware Tech’s website are provided to you only for your convenience. Because external or third party sites are not subject to Delaware Tech’s Privacy Policy, personal information you provide on external or third party sites accessed through such destination links is done at your own risk. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of such external and/or third party sites before providing personal information on such sites.

This Privacy Policy applies strictly to the Delaware Technical Community College Website and is no longer in effect when the user leaves this website.

If you have questions regarding this policy or the Delaware Technical Community College website, please contact our webmaster via [go.dtcc.edu/WebFeedback](http://go.dtcc.edu/WebFeedback).
